[{"answer": "Well, you know, it's a very chilling reminder, Piers, of just how dangerous this whole situation was, especially when this dramatic rescue was carried out by federal agents.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What can you tell me about what we now know about this?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Right, yes.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "She is -- right now she's wonderful.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "How is his mother?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "No, I haven't seen him yet.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Do you know how he is?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I was actually working and was in Troy, Alabama.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "The moment that you heard he was OK, where were you and how soon did you speak to Ethan's mother afterwards?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "So you think he was plotting this all the time?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "We have prayed a lot together, we have talked, we have cried together, we've hugged.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "What have you been able to do in the last week to try and bring her any kind of comfort?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I want to start tonight, Piers, by speaking if I can for a moment about the importance of the significance of this date.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "What is your reaction to what happened today?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I think that there's two things that come to mind immediately.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "What is your view about the longevity of Stand Your Ground as a law in America in any state after this case?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Yes, and that's --", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "And I thought, what on earth are these weapons doing in civilian hands?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "And what is -- what is your answer?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "You know, there's no telling what would have happened.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Now my question to you again is, if your brother had not gone out with a gun that night, you must surely accept that Trayvon Martin would still be alive?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "No, I wasn't there either.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Were you?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "You know, for me, it was a really interesting situation two years ago being there when the young man used a semiautomatic Glock, but the problem was he used an extended magazine.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "You know, I think one of the things that happened that was really great was seeing Gabby last week at the Senate hearing and saying, we need you to be brave and we need you to be courageous because Americans are counting on you, but the problem has been we have Democrats in places like Arizona who are afraid to touch this issue because they're so petrified that if they come out and say, we want to have responsible and commonsense changes to gun safety laws, that they're going to be hammered back at home as being anti-gun.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Well, who are these people and why won't they wear this?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Would you concur with that overview?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "It's basically -- well, the contract is for the Scientology's clergy, which is called the C-Organization.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "What is that?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Known as C-Org?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Yes, it's scientology's most dedicated followers.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "This is like the higher executive level of Scientology, right?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "The reality is that like these pictures, like, you know, these are all rows that we dug, all plants that we planted.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "But what is the reality of this?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "From when I was six until I was 12.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "How long were you doing this for?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Absolutely, it was.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Would you call it child labor?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "We did the labor for four hours a day every day, except on Saturdays we did it all day.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "How many hours a day would you have to do this?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "We saw our parents once a week.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "How much of your parents were you allowed to see?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Yeah, I mean, it was normal.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Did it feel normal because you were around everybody else doing the same thing?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, at the time it was my decision to stay.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "How did that feel to you?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "In six years?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "ILL: I mean, I definitely saw him throughout.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Did you have much to do with him during this period?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Is he an evil man?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "I mean, as a child, you know, of course, the labor that we've already, you know, spoken about.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "In terms of how the evilness, if you like, manifested itself, how would you articulate that?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Right, yes.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "That was because he'd gone to China and he'd seen this happening in Chinese schools and liked the idea of it?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "When I look back, yes, definitely.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Looking back, you must feel completely brainwashed?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I think that the church sold the property, so they no longer own it.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Do they let anybody go on the ranch, any outsiders?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yeah, but the church has a rule that C-Org members can't have children.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Presumably they have places like this elsewhere?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "I mean, I think that either he does know what's going on and he's not talking about it or he is willfully ignorant about it.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "What is your reaction to people like Tom Cruise when you hear him speak like that?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Things like that you wouldn't run across there.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Any child labor?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I think that partially.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Do you think these celebrities are being duped?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Yes, yeah.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "You have a couple of children, I think?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "No, he hasn't spoken to me since I left.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Have you had any direct feedback from him since you left?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "ILL: No, I mean -- well, I mean, my dad -- I mean, not the Scientology ones.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "What about any of his immediate family?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Do they have any contact with him, with David Miscavige?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "So basically once you're out of the church, as far as he's concerned, that's it?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I mean, it should be exposed for the organization that it is.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What should happen to the Church of Scientology?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I mean, read my book.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "And to people who are watching this and saying, well, how do we know she's telling the truth, what do you say to them?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I mean, I've definitely had questions about it and certain things that I didn't understand.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Has it been hard to repair the relationship with your parents, given that it was almost nonexistent through all those young years?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, you're absolutely right, that it is of preeminent importance that we make sure that kids are in a safe and secure environment in our schools.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "What is your view about all the various views put forward about how to make kids safer in schools with the gun debate?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Do you like the idea guns around children generally?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Something has to be done, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "So there are three primary things that we focus on at Students First.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "ORGAN: What are the overview bullet points you would like to see happen which could radically change America's education system to start making it more competitive?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Well, teachers don't go into the profession because of the money.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "You got to pay them more to get that kind of teacher?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "That is exactly right.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "But I think too many of them may leave if they feel disincentivised, right?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Second point is we have to empower parents with information and with choices, so that no family ever is in a situation where they feel like they're trapped in a failing school.", "docId": "130205pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Second point?", "qSentId": 644}]